megadownlinebuilder.com 2011-12-16

# 

This privacy statement discloses the privacy practices for http://www.megadownlinebuilder.com

**Information Collection and Use of Information**  
In order to use this website, a user must first complete the registration form. During registration a user is required to give his contact information (name and email address). This information is used to contact the user about the service on our site for which he has expressed interest. We will not sell, share, or rent personal information to others.

**Security**  
This website takes every precaution to protect our users personal information. When a user submits sensitive information via our site, his information is protected both online and off-line. Only the administrator of this site can access personal information of the users. 

**Correction/Updating Personal Information**  
If a user's personally identifiable information changes, we provide a way to correct that user's personal data provided to us. This can be done within the member area.

**Right to Cancel**  
Our users can cancel membership by contacting our support. We will remove your email and other information when you cancel. You will not receive any contact after your cancellation.

**Site and Service Updates**  
We may send the user site and service announcement updates. We communicate with the users to provide requested services and in regards to issues relating to their accounts via email.

**Notification of Changes**  
If we decide to change our Privacy Policy we will notify users by way of an email. Users will have a choice as to whether or not we use their information in this different manner. 

Copyright © 2011 MegaDownlineBuilder team. All Rights Reserved
